---
http_interactions:
- request:
    method: get
    uri: https://critterism-be.herokuapp.com/api/v1/trivia
    body:
      encoding: US-ASCII
      string: ''
    headers:
      User-Agent:
      - Faraday v2.6.0
      Accept-Encoding:
      - gzip;q=1.0,deflate;q=0.6,identity;q=0.3
      Accept:
      - "*/*"
  response:
    status:
      code: 200
      message: OK
    headers:
      Server:
      - Cowboy
      Date:
      - Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:24:07 GMT
      Connection:
      - keep-alive
      Content-Type:
      - application/json; charset=utf-8
      Etag:
      - W/"4219f594dbffeb95356fcd9940da0438"
      Cache-Control:
      - max-age=0, private, must-revalidate
      X-Request-Id:
      - e4a7cf59-e0aa-4fee-b0a5-e4bbef18086c
      X-Runtime:
      - '0.032548'
      Transfer-Encoding:
      - chunked
      Via:
      - 1.1 vegur
    body:
      encoding: UTF-8
      string: '{"data":[{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A
        slug\u0026rsquo;s blood is green.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"],"answers":["False","True"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kangaroos
        keep food in their pouches next to their children.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"],"answers":["True","False"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","question":"What
        is the scientific name of the Budgerigar?","correct_answer":"Melopsittacus
        undulatus","incorrect_answers":["Nymphicus hollandicus","Pyrrhura molinae","Ara
        macao"],"answers":["Nymphicus hollandicus","Pyrrhura molinae","Ara macao","Melopsittacus
        undulatus"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"Which
        animal was part of an Russian domestication experiment in 1959?","correct_answer":"Foxes","incorrect_answers":["Pigeons","Bears","Alligators"],"answers":["Pigeons","Bears","Alligators","Foxes"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"Which
        class of animals are newts members of?","correct_answer":"Amphibian","incorrect_answers":["Fish","Reptiles","Mammals"],"answers":["Fish","Reptiles","Mammals","Amphibian"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A
        caterpillar has more muscles than humans do.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"],"answers":["False","True"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The
        Killer Whale is considered a type of dolphin.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"],"answers":["False","True"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"medium","question":"What
        is the fastest animal?","correct_answer":"Peregrine Falcon","incorrect_answers":["Golden
        Eagle","Cheetah","Horsefly"],"answers":["Golden Eagle","Cheetah","Horsefly","Peregrine
        Falcon"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"What
        colour is the female blackbird?","correct_answer":"Brown","incorrect_answers":["Black","White","Yellow"],"answers":["Black","White","Yellow","Brown"]}},{"id":null,"type":"trivia","attributes":{"category":"Animals","type":"multiple","difficulty":"easy","question":"How
        many teeth does an adult rabbit have?","correct_answer":"28","incorrect_answers":["30","26","24"],"answers":["30","26","24","28"]}}]}'
  recorded_at: Tue, 08 Nov 2022 22:24:07 GMT
recorded_with: VCR 6.1.0
